{
    "subject": "resource/Department_of_Health_(Philippines)",
    "predicate": "ontology/headquarter",
    "object": "resource/Manila",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of the Department of Health (Philippines) are located in Manila.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887924790382385,
            "question": "Is Manila the location of the Department of Health (Philippines) headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9885643124580383,
            "question": "Where are the headquarters of the Department of Health (Philippines) located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9852917194366455,
            "question": "Where can you find the Department of Health (Philippines) headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9847751259803772,
            "question": "What is the location of the Philippines' Department of Health headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9813011884689331,
            "question": "What city serves as the headquarters for the Philippines' Department of Health?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9810373187065125,
            "question": "In which Philippine city is the Department of Health headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9677679538726807,
            "question": "Which city houses the Philippine Department of Health headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9610313177108765,
            "question": "Where is the Department of Health (Philippines) based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8251013159751892,
            "question": "What city serves as the home for the Philippines' Department of Health?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7572532892227173,
            "question": "Which Philippine city is home to the Department of Health?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of the Department of Health (Philippines) are located in Manila.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2876_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city serves as the home for the Philippines' Department of Health?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2876_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is the Department of Health (Philippines) based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2876_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city houses the Philippine Department of Health headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2876_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2876_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the structured JSON format with the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all three documents mention the headquarters of the Department of Health (Philippines) as being located at the San Lazaro Compound, along Rizal Avenue in Manila."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents indicate that the Philippine Department of Health has its headquarters at the San Lazaro Compound, along Rizal Avenue in Manila. Therefore, the statement that the headquarters of the Department of Health (Philippines) are located in Manila is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}